{
    "subject": "resource/On\u00e1n_Barreiros",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Spanish_sailors",
    "human_readable": "On\u00e1n Barreiros is about Spanish sailors.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.765505850315094,
            "question": "Who is On\u00e1n Barreiros?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7231496572494507,
            "question": "What are Spanish sailors known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6569868922233582,
            "question": "Can you tell me about famous Spanish sailors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6243278980255127,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Spanish sailors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.598327100276947,
            "question": "Where did Spanish sailors traditionally sail to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5434285998344421,
            "question": "What role did Spanish sailors play in history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.520310640335083,
            "question": "How has the role of Spanish sailors changed over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5118505954742432,
            "question": "What are some important historical events involving Spanish sailors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36230742931365967,
            "question": "What skills and qualities are important for Spanish sailors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05901375412940979,
            "question": "Are there any famous sailing expeditions led by Spaniards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=On\u00e1n Barreiros is about Spanish sailors.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1091_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What skills and qualities are important for Spanish sailors?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1091_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some important historical events involving Spanish sailors?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1091_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has the role of Spanish sailors changed over time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1091_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1091_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1091_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1091_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1091_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1091_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1091_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1091_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1091_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1091_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1091_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information provided mentions On\u00e1n Barreiros as a Spanish sailor, which supports the statement that On\u00e1n Barreiros is related to Spanish sailors."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}